<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><addons>
  <addon provider-name="elgatito" name="Elementum" id="plugin.video.elementum" version="0.1.1120001">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.0.0"/>
      <import addon="repository.elementumorg" optional="true"/>
      <import addon="script.module.kodi-six"/>
      <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
      <import addon="repository.service.elementum" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension library="navigation.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
      <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension library="service.py" start="startup" point="xbmc.service"/>
    <extension library="resources/site-packages" point="xbmc.python.module"/>
    <extension library="navigation.py" point="xbmc.subtitle.module"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="ru">Elementum: Стриминг видео</summary>
      <summary lang="en">Elementum: Media streaming</summary>
      <summary lang="hr">Elementum: Medijsko strujanje</summary>
      <summary lang="es">Elementum: Transmisión de medios</summary>
      <summary lang="sv">Elementum: medieströmning</summary>
      <description lang="ru">Elementum это дополнение для поиска и воспроизведения торрентов. Дополнение не ходит на запрещенные сайты самостоятельно. Хотя, для поиска используются дополнения (называемые провайдерами), которые устанавливаются отдельно.[CR]Этот проект является ответвлением хорошо извесных, но не поддерживаемых Pulsar/Quasar от steeve и scakemyer.</description>
      <description lang="en">Elementum is a torrent finding and streaming engine. It doesn't go on torrent websites for legal reasons. However, it calls specially crafted add-ons (called providers) that are installed separately.[CR]This project is a fork of the well known, but no longer maintained Pulsar/Quasar projects from steeve and scakemyer.</description>
      <description lang="hr">Elementum je pogon pretraživanja i strujanja. Ne posjećuje torrent web stranice iz pravnih razloga. Ipak, koristi posebno napravljene dodatke (nazvane pružatelji usluge) koji su instalirani odvojeno.[CR]Ovaj projekt je ogranak dobro poznatih, ali više ne održavanih Pulsar/Quasar projekata od autora steevea i scakemyera.</description>
      <description lang="es">Elementum es un motor de búsqueda y transmisión torrent. No navega por sitios web torrent por razones legales. Sin embargo, llama a complementos especialmente diseñados para ello (denominados providers o proveedores) que se instalan por separado.[CR]Este proyecto es un fork de los bien conocidos, pero ya sin soporte proyectos Pulsar/Quasar de steeve y scakemyer.[CR]</description>
      <description lang="sv">Elementum är en torrentsöknings- och strömningsmotor. Det går inte till torrentwebbplatser av juridiska skäl. Den anropar dock speciellt utformade tillägg (kallade leverantörer) som installeras separat.[CR]Detta projekt är en förgrening av de välkända, men inte längre underhållna Pulsar/Quasar-projekten av steeve och scakemyer. </description>
      <disclaimer lang="ru">Автор дополнения не несёт ответственности за скачивание или поиск информации и содержимого в этом дополнении. Автор никак не связан с Kodi, командой Kodi, или XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="en">The author does not own or host any content found within this Addon. The author is not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="hr">Autor ovog dodatka ne posjeduje i ne distribuira bilo kakav sadržaj koji je pronađen. Autor nije povezan sa ili na bilo koji drugi način bilo sa Kodijem, Team Kodijem ili XBMC fundacijom.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="es">El autor no posee ni aloja ningún contenido que se encuentre a través de este complemento. El autor no está unido ni relacionado de ninguna manera con Kodi, Team Kodi, o XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
      <disclaimer lang="sv">Skaparen äger inte eller är värd av något innehåll som finns i detta tillägg. Författaren är inte ansluten till eller på något annat sätt en del av Kodi, Team Kodi eller XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
      <language>en el es de fi fr he hr it nl pt ro sk sv</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://elementum.surge.sh/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/elgatito/plugin.video.elementum</source>
      <forum/>
      <license>Non commercial. See https://github.com/elgatito/plugin.video.elementum/blob/master/LICENSE</license>
      <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshots/home.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshots/movies.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshots/webui.png</screenshot>
      </assets>
    </extension>
  </addon>
  <addon provider-name="ElementumOrg" name="lt2http" id="service.lt2http" version="0.0.160043">
    <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="16.0.0"/>
      <import addon="repository.elementum" optional="true"/>
      <import addon="script.module.kodi-six"/>
      <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
    </requires>
    <extension library="navigation.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"/>
    <extension library="service.py" start="startup" point="xbmc.service"/>
    <extension library="resources/site-packages" point="xbmc.python.module"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <summary lang="en">LT2http: LibTorrent-to-HTTP streaming addon</summary>
      <description lang="en">LT2http is a torrent download and streaming engine.</description>
      <disclaimer lang="en">The author does not own or host any content found within this Addon. The author is not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.</disclaimer>
      <language>en el es de fi fr he hr it nl pt ro sk</language>
      <platform>all</platform>
      <website>http://elementum.surge.sh/</website>
      <source>https://github.com/ElementumOrg/lt2http</source>
      <forum/>
      <license>Non commercial. See https://github.com/ElementumOrg/service/blob/master/LICENSE</license>
      <assets>
        <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
      </assets>
    </extension>
  </addon>
</addons>
